domainname.com 2013-04-01

# Privacy Policy - DomainName, Inc.

DomainName.com respects your privacy. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to you, our customer. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the site [www.domainname.com](http://www.domainname.com/).

  * We do not give third parties access to your personal information. 
  * We only send e-mail or postal mail to you if you have elected to receive it.* 
  * If we determine that any account with us is being used for the purpose of sending spam, we will take action to shut it down as soon as possible. 

Since domain name registration information is available to the public, anyone can access it through "whois" searches. At times our customers may have been included within these searches. However, the spam they received does not in any way come from DomainName.

We will never give any information about you to others without your express permission. Our site uses forms in which you give us contact information (like your name, address, and e-mail address) so you can place orders, request information etc. We use your customer information only when it will be important for us to contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, our web site, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable.

We use information gathered about you from our site statistics (for example your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your session information. We also use cookies to store your username if you request to remember your username during login. That information will be used to pre-fill the login form at a later time. If you are referred to our website through an ad or a partner, we will store the referral information in the cookies.

Our site also contains links to other third party Web sites. DomainName.com ([www.domainname.com](http://www.domainname.com/)) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use 256 bit SSL security to encrypt any transmissions when you provide credit card information, personal data, etc.

**Sending Emails**  
We use e-mails to communicate with you, to confirm your placed orders, and to send information that you have requested. You can contact us directly using the email address [support@domainname.com](mailto:support@domainname.com) or “Submit Ticket” page. We strive to promptly reply to your messages.  
The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve our site and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded. However, your information will only be shared with third parties with your explicit permission.

**Only If We Have To**  
As stated previously in this policy, we will never give out your information without your permission. The only exceptions to this are, when we are required by law, in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or we must comply with a legal process served on our web site.

**Changes In Our Practices**  
If we change our information handling practices or other privacy aspects, we will post those changes on this privacy statement, at least 7 days prior to their implementation. Please review our privacy policies from time to time to know about the changes. We may also try to notify you through e-mail of the privacy changes if necessary.

**Credit Card Processor**  
We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. If you would like to know more about privacy policies of our credit card processing company, you may e-mail us at [support@domainname.com](mailto:support@domainname.com).

**Contests**  
From time to time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to respond and disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and e-mail address. DomainName will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. DomainName does not store this information in the database but uses it just to send the one-time e-mail.

**Personal Information Following Termination of Account**  
When Your DomainName account is cancelled (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your personally identifiable information is placed in "deactivated" status within our corresponding databases. However, you should know that deactivation of your account does not mean your personally identifiable information has been deleted from our database entirely. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information if necessary in order to resolve disputes or enforce our agreements.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you can contact DomainName  at [support@domainname.com](mailto:support@domainname.com). You may also contact us at:

_11400 W. Olympic Blvd.  
Suite 200  
Los Angeles, California 90064  
United States_ _ ___  
[_support@domainname.com_](mailto:support@domainname.com) _ ___

* The e-mail and/or postal mail you elect to receive may include offerings from trusted DomainName advertising partners. We never sell your personal information for these offerings.
